const Science=[{question:"What species is the closest living relative to humans ?.",answers:[{text:"Chimpanzees",correct:!0},{text:"Gorilla",correct:!1},{text:"Monkey",correct:!1},{text:"Hyena",correct:!1}]},{question:"What's the base unit of mass in the metric system ?.",answers:[{text:"Kilowatt",correct:!1},{text:"Kilometer",correct:!1},{text:"Kiloliter",correct:!1},{text:"Kilogram",correct:!0}]},{question:"In what galaxy is the solar system located ?.",answers:[{text:"Saturn",correct:!1},{text:"Pluto",correct:!1},{text:"Milky Way",correct:!0},{text:"Mars",correct:!1}]},{question:"What O-word describes oxygen with molecules that have three atoms instead of two ?.",answers:[{text:"Omitte",correct:!1},{text:"Ozone",correct:!0},{text:"Oburne",correct:!1},{text:"Odine",correct:!1}]},{question:"How many of the nine planets have moons ?.",answers:[{text:"Nine",correct:!1},{text:"Seven",correct:!0},{text:"One",correct:!1},{text:"Five",correct:!1}]},{question:"What cooking fuel is produced by heating wood without oxygen ?.",answers:[{text:"Gas",correct:!1},{text:"Charcoal",correct:!0},{text:"Wood",correct:!1},{text:"Thermite",correct:!1}]},{question:"What type of trees yield the resin used to produce turpentine ?.",answers:[{text:"WhiteOak tree",correct:!1},{text:"Gum tree ",correct:!1},{text:"Mango tree",correct:!1},{text:"Pine tree",correct:!0}]},{question:"What's the most malleable metal ?.",answers:[{text:"Copper",correct:!1},{text:"Aluminum ",correct:!1},{text:"Brass",correct:!1},{text:"Gold",correct:!0}]},{question:"What continent is subjected to the world's largest ozone hole ?.",answers:[{text:"Antarctica",correct:!0},{text:"Iceland",correct:!1},{text:"Africa",correct:!1},{text:"Europe",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the chemical formula for water ?.",answers:[{text:"O2Q",correct:!1},{text:"S2O",correct:!1},{text:"H2Q",correct:!1},{text:"H2O",correct:!0}]},{question:"What process involves heating an ore to obtain a metal ?.",answers:[{text:"Brazing",correct:!1},{text:"Graining",correct:!1},{text:"Smelting",correct:!0},{text:"Mulping",correct:!1}]},{question:"What's removed from water in the process of desalination ?.",answers:[{text:"Salt",correct:!0},{text:"Sugar",correct:!1},{text:"Germs",correct:!1},{text:"Mineral",correct:!1}]},{question:"What planet is closest in size to our moon ?.",answers:[{text:"Mars",correct:!1},{text:"Jupiter",correct:!1},{text:"Mercury",correct:!0},{text:"Pluto",correct:!1}]},{question:'What type of mineral is pencil "lead" made from ?.',answers:[{text:"Coal",correct:!1},{text:"Graphite",correct:!0},{text:"Iron ore",correct:!1},{text:"Sulphate",correct:!1}]},{question:"What color does litmus turn when dipped into acid ?.",answers:[{text:"Red",correct:!1},{text:"Pink",correct:!0},{text:"Blue",correct:!1},{text:"Black",correct:!1}]},{question:"What's the only metal that's not a solid at room temperature ?.",answers:[{text:"Mercury",correct:!0},{text:"Valarian Steel",correct:!1},{text:"Iron ore",correct:!1},{text:"Gold",correct:!1}]},{question:"What's the common name for a cubic decimeter ?.",answers:[{text:"A cubic",correct:!1},{text:"A liter",correct:!0},{text:"A milimeter",correct:!1},{text:"A gram",correct:!1}]}];export default Science;